[{"layer": 6, "results": [{"multiplier": 1000, "answers": [{"question": "\"ok never going back to this place again.\" \"", "answer": ["ok never going back to this place again.", "ok never going back to this place again.", "ok never going back to this place again.", "ok never going back to this place again.", "ok never going back to this place again."]}, {"question": "\"easter day nothing open, heard about this place figured it would ok.\" \"", "answer": ["easter day nothing open, heard about this place figured it would ok.", "easter day nothing open, heard about this place figured it would ok.", "easter day nothing open, heard about this place figured it would ok.", "easter day nothing open, heard about this place figured it would ok.", "easter day nothing open, heard about this place figured it would ok."]}, {"question": "\"the host that walked us to the table and left without a word.\" \"", "answer": ["the host that walked us to the table and left without a word.", "the host that walked us to the table and left without a word.", "the host that walked us to the table and left without a word.", "the host that walked us to the table and left without a word.", "the host that walked us to the table and left without a word."]}, {"question": "\"it just gets worse.\" \"", "answer": ["it just gets worse.", "it just gets worse.", "it just gets worse.", "it just gets worse.", "it just gets worse."]}, {"question": "\"the food tasted awful.\" \"", "answer": ["the food tasted awful.", "the food tasted awful.", "the food tasted awful.", "the food tasted awful.", "the food tasted awful."]}, {"question": "\"no sign of the manager.\" \"", "answer": ["no sign of the manager.", "no sign of the manager.", "no sign of the manager.", "no sign of the manager.", "no sign of the manager."]}, {"question": "\"the last couple years this place has been going down hill.\" \"", "answer": ["the last couple years this place has been going down hill.", "the last couple years this place has been going down hill.", "the last couple years this place has been going down hill.", "the last couple years this place has been going down hill.", "the last couple years this place has been going down hill."]}, {"question": "\"last night however it was way to thick and tasteless.\" \"", "answer": ["last night however it was way to thick and tasteless.", "last night however it was way to thick and tasteless.", "last night however it was way to thick and tasteless.", "last night however it was way to thick and tasteless.", "last night however it was way to thick and tasteless."]}, {"question": "\"it smelled like rotten urine.\" \"", "answer": ["it smelled like rotten urine.", "it smelled like rotten urine.", "it smelled like rotten urine.", "it smelled like rotten urine.", "it smelled like rotten urine."]}, {"question": "\"i am not exaggerating.\" \"", "answer": ["i am not exaggerating.", "i am not exaggerating.", "i am not exaggerating.", "i am not exaggerating.", "i am not exaggerating."]}]}]}, {"layer": 7, "results": [{"multiplier": 1000, "answers": [{"question": "\"ok never going back to this place again.\" \"", "answer": ["ok never going back to this place again.", "ok never going back to this place again.", "ok never going back to this place again.", "ok never going back to this place again.", "ok never going back to this place again."]}, {"question": "\"easter day nothing open, heard about this place figured it would ok.\" \"", "answer": ["easter day nothing open, heard about this place figured it would ok.", "easter day nothing open, heard about this place figured it would ok.", "easter day nothing open, heard about this place figured it would ok.", "easter day nothing open, heard about this place figured it would ok.", "easter day nothing open, heard about this place figured it would ok."]}, {"question": "\"the host that walked us to the table and left without a word.\" \"", "answer": ["the host that walked us to the table and left without a word.", "the host that walked us to the table and left without a word.", "the host that walked us to the table and left without a word.", "the host that walked us to the table and left without a word.", "the host that walked us to the table and left without a word."]}, {"question": "\"it just gets worse.\" \"", "answer": ["it just gets worse.", "it just gets worse.", "it just gets worse.", "it just gets worse.", "it just gets worse."]}, {"question": "\"the food tasted awful.\" \"", "answer": ["the food tasted awful.", "the food tasted awful.", "the food tasted awful.", "the food tasted awful.", "the food tasted awful."]}, {"question": "\"no sign of the manager.\" \"", "answer": ["no sign of the manager.", "no sign of the manager.", "no sign of the manager.", "no sign of the manager.", "no sign of the manager."]}, {"question": "\"the last couple years this place has been going down hill.\" \"", "answer": ["the last couple years this place has been going down hill.", "the last couple years this place has been going down hill.", "the last couple years this place has been going down hill.", "the last couple years this place has been going down hill.", "the last couple years this place has been going down hill."]}, {"question": "\"last night however it was way to thick and tasteless.\" \"", "answer": ["last night however it was way to thick and tasteless.", "last night however it was way to thick and tasteless.", "last night however it was way to thick and tasteless.", "last night however it was way to thick and tasteless.", "last night however it was way to thick and tasteless."]}, {"question": "\"it smelled like rotten urine.\" \"", "answer": ["it smelled like rotten urine.", "it smelled like rotten urine.", "it smelled like rotten urine.", "it smelled like rotten urine.", "it smelled like rotten urine."]}, {"question": "\"i am not exaggerating.\" \"", "answer": ["i am not exaggerating.", "i am not exaggerating.", "i am not exaggerating.", "i am not exaggerating.", "i am not exaggerating."]}]}]}, {"layer": 8, "results": [{"multiplier": 1000, "answers": [{"question": "\"ok never going back to this place again.\" \"", "answer": ["ok never going back to this place again.", "ok never going back to this place again.", "ok never going back to this place again.", "ok never going back to this place again.", "ok never going back to this place again."]}, {"question": "\"easter day nothing open, heard about this place figured it would ok.\" \"", "answer": ["easter day nothing open, heard about this place figured it would ok.", "easter day nothing open, heard about this place figured it would ok.", "easter day nothing open, heard about this place figured it would ok.", "easter day nothing open, heard about this place figured it would ok.", "easter day nothing open, heard about this place figured it would ok."]}, {"question": "\"the host that walked us to the table and left without a word.\" \"", "answer": ["the host that walked us to the table and left without a word.", "the host that walked us to the table and left without a word.", "the host that walked us to the table and left without a word.", "the host that walked us to the table and left without a word.", "the host that walked us to the table and left without a word."]}, {"question": "\"it just gets worse.\" \"", "answer": ["it just gets worse.", "it just gets worse.", "it just gets worse.", "it just gets worse.", "it just gets worse."]}, {"question": "\"the food tasted awful.\" \"", "answer": ["the food tasted awful.", "the food tasted awful.", "the food tasted awful.", "the food tasted awful.", "the food tasted awful."]}, {"question": "\"no sign of the manager.\" \"", "answer": ["no sign of the manager.", "no sign of the manager.", "no sign of the manager.", "no sign of the manager.", "no sign of the manager."]}, {"question": "\"the last couple years this place has been going down hill.\" \"", "answer": ["the last couple years this place has been going down hill.", "the last couple years this place has been going down hill.", "the last couple years this place has been going down hill.", "the last couple years this place has been going down hill.", "the last couple years this place has been going down hill."]}, {"question": "\"last night however it was way to thick and tasteless.\" \"", "answer": ["last night however it was way to thick and tasteless.", "last night however it was way to thick and tasteless.", "last night however it was way to thick and tasteless.", "last night however it was way to thick and tasteless.", "last night however it was way to thick and tasteless."]}, {"question": "\"it smelled like rotten urine.\" \"", "answer": ["it smelled like rotten urine.", "it smelled like rotten urine.", "it smelled like rotten urine.", "it smelled like rotten urine.", "it smelled like rotten urine."]}, {"question": "\"i am not exaggerating.\" \"", "answer": ["i am not exaggerating.", "i am not exaggerating.", "i am not exaggerating.", "i am not exaggerating.", "i am not exaggerating."]}]}]}, {"layer": 9, "results": [{"multiplier": 1000, "answers": [{"question": "\"ok never going back to this place again.\" \"", "answer": ["ok never going back to this place again.", "ok never going back to this place again.", "ok never going back to this place again.", "ok never going back to this place again.", "ok never going back to this place again."]}, {"question": "\"easter day nothing open, heard about this place figured it would ok.\" \"", "answer": ["easter day nothing open, heard about this place figured it would ok.", "easter day nothing open, heard about this place figured it would ok.", "easter day nothing open, heard about this place figured it would ok.", "easter day nothing open, heard about this place figured it would ok.", "easter day nothing open, heard about this place figured it would ok."]}, {"question": "\"the host that walked us to the table and left without a word.\" \"", "answer": ["the host that walked us to the table and left without a word.", "the host that walked us to the table and left without a word.", "the host that walked us to the table and left without a word.", "the host that walked us to the table and left without a word.", "the host that walked us to the table and left without a word."]}, {"question": "\"it just gets worse.\" \"", "answer": ["it just gets worse.", "it just gets worse.", "it just gets worse.", "it just gets worse.", "it just gets worse."]}, {"question": "\"the food tasted awful.\" \"", "answer": ["the food tasted awful.", "the food tasted awful.", "the food tasted awful.", "the food tasted awful.", "the food tasted awful."]}, {"question": "\"no sign of the manager.\" \"", "answer": ["no sign of the manager.", "no sign of the manager.", "no sign of the manager.", "no sign of the manager.", "no sign of the manager."]}, {"question": "\"the last couple years this place has been going down hill.\" \"", "answer": ["the last couple years this place has been going down hill.", "the last couple years this place has been going down hill.", "the last couple years this place has been going down hill.", "the last couple years this place has been going down hill.", "the last couple years this place has been going down hill."]}, {"question": "\"last night however it was way to thick and tasteless.\" \"", "answer": ["last night however it was way to thick and tasteless.", "last night however it was way to thick and tasteless.", "last night however it was way to thick and tasteless.", "last night however it was way to thick and tasteless.", "last night however it was way to thick and tasteless."]}, {"question": "\"it smelled like rotten urine.\" \"", "answer": ["it smelled like rotten urine.", "it smelled like rotten urine.", "it smelled like rotten urine.", "it smelled like rotten urine.", "it smelled like rotten urine."]}, {"question": "\"i am not exaggerating.\" \"", "answer": ["i am not exaggerating.", "i am not exaggerating.", "i am not exaggerating.", "i am not exaggerating.", "i am not exaggerating."]}]}]}, {"layer": 10, "results": [{"multiplier": 1000, "answers": [{"question": "\"ok never going back to this place again.\" \"", "answer": ["ok never going back to this place again.", "ok never going back to this place again.", "ok never going back to this place again.", "ok never going back to this place again.", "ok never going back to this place again."]}, {"question": "\"easter day nothing open, heard about this place figured it would ok.\" \"", "answer": ["easter day nothing open, heard about this place figured it would ok.", "easter day nothing open, heard about this place figured it would ok.", "easter day nothing open, heard about this place figured it would ok.", "easter day nothing open, heard about this place figured it would ok.", "easter day nothing open, heard about this place figured it would ok."]}, {"question": "\"the host that walked us to the table and left without a word.\" \"", "answer": ["the host that walked us to the table and left without a word.", "the host that walked us to the table and left without a word.", "the host that walked us to the table and left without a word.", "the host that walked us to the table and left without a word.", "the host that walked us to the table and left without a word."]}, {"question": "\"it just gets worse.\" \"", "answer": ["it just gets worse.", "it just gets worse.", "it just gets worse.", "it just gets worse.", "it just gets worse."]}, {"question": "\"the food tasted awful.\" \"", "answer": ["the food tasted awful.", "the food tasted awful.", "the food tasted awful.", "the food tasted awful.", "the food tasted awful."]}, {"question": "\"no sign of the manager.\" \"", "answer": ["no sign of the manager.", "no sign of the manager.", "no sign of the manager.", "no sign of the manager.", "no sign of the manager."]}, {"question": "\"the last couple years this place has been going down hill.\" \"", "answer": ["the last couple years this place has been going down hill.", "the last couple years this place has been going down hill.", "the last couple years this place has been going down hill.", "the last couple years this place has been going down hill.", "the last couple years this place has been going down hill."]}, {"question": "\"last night however it was way to thick and tasteless.\" \"", "answer": ["last night however it was way to thick and tasteless.", "last night however it was way to thick and tasteless.", "last night however it was way to thick and tasteless.", "last night however it was way to thick and tasteless.", "last night however it was way to thick and tasteless."]}, {"question": "\"it smelled like rotten urine.\" \"", "answer": ["it smelled like rotten urine.", "it smelled like rotten urine.", "it smelled like rotten urine.", "it smelled like rotten urine.", "it smelled like rotten urine."]}, {"question": "\"i am not exaggerating.\" \"", "answer": ["i am not exaggerating.", "i am not exaggerating.", "i am not exaggerating.", "i am not exaggerating.", "i am not exaggerating."]}]}]}]